Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of art Womens Committee records, circa 1960-2001 COR0008.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art Women's Committee records
circa 1905-2001
Circa 1955 - 2001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
COR0008.1.RG
33 Linear Feet
For several years prior to the forming of the Women's Committee, the Director and staff of the Corcoran had noted the success of volunteer help in other museums and with hopes of obtaining the same kind of substantive help, the Women's Committee was formed October 1953 to assist the Director and to provoke public interest. The records of the Women's Committee cover all aspects of the Committee's activities and include: minutes, annual reports, ball reports, art tour reports, bylaws, treasurers' books, correspondence, subscription lists, lecture possibilities, and sample tickets. The materials in this record group date from approximately 1905-2001 with the bulk falling between approximately 1955-2001.
Conditions Governing Access
For RG that are open for research:
This collection is open to research.
When conducting research within The Corcoran Archives collections, pleased be advised of the following exceptions:
Records of the Board of Trustees (RG 1.0) and records of the Office of the Director (RG 2.0) are closed to research for 25 years from the date of creation.
Development records are closed to research (RG 3.2).
Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for the lifetime of the student, and are presumed to be open 75 years after the date of record creation (RG 9.0 Series 4).
Personnel and financial records are closed for 50 years from date of record creation (RG 4.0).
Please see the Public Services and Instruction Librarian for assistance.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Corcoran Institution Board of Trustees donated these records to The George Washington University in 2016.
Arrangement
Organized into 12 series: Administration; Activities; Treasurer's records; Ephemera; Women's Committee files; Minutes, meeting files, and reports; Lectures and tours; Balls files; Trips; Scrapbooks; Janet Lundgren and Carolyn Amiot subject files; and Jeannette Petite and Maud Brown subject files.
[Please note: the first 4 series were part of a processing project undertaken in the 1980s and series 5-12 were part of a processing project undertaken in 2016]
Historical narrative
The first section of this history, covering events through 1981, was prepared by Corcoran Archivist Katherine M. Kovocs for publication in 1985 with the support of the National Endowment for the Humanities.
For several years prior to the forming of the Women's Committee, the Director and staff of the Corcoran had noted the success of volunteer help in other museums and with hopes of obtaining the same kind of substantive help, the Women's Committee was formed October 1953 to assist the Director and to provoke public interest.
In the early years, the Women's Committee was concerned chiefly with the entertainment of artists, performing musicians or lecturers at the Gallery, and in helping promote interest in membership. As the various needs of the Gallery grew, fundraising and public relations were added to the sphere of the Committee's influence.
The Women's Committee inaugurated its first ball held February 24, 1956 at the Corcoran, a major fundraising benefit for the Gallery.
In October 1956 the Wednesday morning lecture series was initiated for subscribers. The series was enormously successful and also raised funds for the Gallery.
A docents program was formed in 1958 but was disbanded because the Gallery did not have a curator of education. Both the Gallery and the Women's Committee believed that a successful docent program required professional direction, staff support for scheduling and a formal training program for the docents themselves to reflect the scholarly tradition of the Gallery. In 1963 the docent program was reactivated with funds provided by the Women's Committee. This covered salaries for a Curator of Education, his assistant and monies for a supporting program. The docents, now numbering 50, conduct thousands of children and adults through the Gallery each year.
Another fundraising and public relations activity was the annual tour of private art collections, which were successfully continued for 7 seasons and raised substantial sums for the Gallery.
Some of the gifts to the Gallery include: a kitchen (costing $6,000); the renovation of the Auditorium (costing $28,000 - under the direction of Mrs. James O. Denby); financing the reframing and restoration of 55 paintings in the Corcoran Collection which made up an exhibition entitled "Masterpieces of the Corcoran Gallery of Art" held at the Wildenstein Gallery, New York, as a benefit for the Corcoran, profiting $4,500; furnishing a student's lounge in the Art School (gift of Mrs. Robert Van Roijen); furnishing a library for the Art School (Mrs. Atherton Macondray gave the furniture in memory of her children's grandfather, E.F. Andrews, first Principal of the Art School); furnishing and renovation of an area for a children's gallery (gift of Mrs. John Logan); contribution of $3,500 for "The Night of Stars" Ball by Woodward and Lothrop (through Mrs. Tompkins Parker's efforts); also the planting of camellias and azaleas at the entrance to the Gallery by the Camellia Society (by Mrs. Tompkins Parker); helping to raise the sum of $50,000 at the 100th anniversary year during the Gallery Membership Campaign -- Mrs. Heath C. Moorman, chairman, with a group from the Women's Committee, assisted Mr. William J. Flather, Jr.; $67,000 was appropriated for installing the new Museum Shop at the Gallery in 1970.
The By-Laws of the Corcoran Women's Committee state the "purpose shall be to cooperate with the Board of Trustees and the Director of the Corcoran Gallery of Art in extending the activities and usefulness of the Gallery as a cultural and educational institution." The Women's Committee has certainly fulfilled and continues to fulfill the great needs of the Gallery in "activities and usefulness".
The following section of this history was prepared in 2019 by George Washington University SCRC staff with the support of the Luce Foundation.
By 1998 the mission statement for the Women's Committee had expanded to include the Art School: "The purpose of the Women's Committee shall be to support the activities and events of the Gallery and to promote the Gallery as a cultural and educational institution in cooperation with the Board of Trustees, the Director of the Gallery and the Dean of the Art School."
Throughout the 1980s and 1990s, the Women's Committee continued to act as an important organizer and funder of projects, programs, and art acquisition at the Corcoran Gallery of Art. The Annual Corcoran Ball was the most prominent event managed by the Women's Committee, with proceeds going to the Committee's funds, and from there distributed at the Committee's discretion to the Corcoran Gallery itself, or towards operation and acquisition cost for the Women's Committee. Funds raised by the Ball routinely surpassed $300,000 and often factored into the yearly budget of the Gallery itself. The Corcoran Ball was last held in 2015.
In April of 1984 the Women's Committee established the Argentina Copello Dudley Memorial Lecture series, and annual educational lecture program managed by the Women's Committee and conducted at the Corcoran Gallery or art. Management of the lecture series was taken over by the Corcoran Gallery in 1998.
Other educational opportunities provided by the Women's Committee to its members included behind-the-scenes tours, overseas tours to museums, and joint education programs with the Friends of the Corcoran, a donor organization which Women's Committee members were encouraged to join as part of the Committee's membership requirements.
In 1998, the women's committee created a tier of membership called Diplomatic Associate Member in order to include individuals in the diplomatic community whose responsibilities and residence might have otherwise prevented them from joining or taking leadership roles in the Women's Committee.
The Corcoran Women's Committee exists as an independent volunteer organization, and continues past the Corcoran Gallery's dissolution and the sale of the art school to George Washington University.
The Corcoran Women's Committee has become an arts study and philanthropy group, establishing a Grant Program in order to encourage individual visual artists, the fine arts, and arts education in the Washington, D.C. metropolitan area. In May of 2018, the Corcoran Women's Committee selected CulturalDC and its Mobile Art Gallery as the first recipient of the new Grant Program.
Custodial History
The processed portions of the Women's Committee records were transferred to the Archives in 1981.
Scope and Contents
The records of the Women's Committee cover all aspects of the Committee's activities and include: minutes, annual reports, ball reports, art tour reports, bylaws, treasurers' books, correspondence, subscription lists, lecture possibilities, and sample tickets.
Separated Materials
The following records were discarded: duplicates, extra stationary, handwritten notes and outdated 3x5 cards showing ticket payments for previous balls.
During processing the following records were removed to another location:
News clippings -- New Location: Artist clipping files or history clipping files Press releases -- New Location: Public relations press release series
- Administration, 1962-1984; Series 1; 1.5 Cubic Feet
  Arrangement
  Organized into three subseries: Mintues, Annual reports and By-laws
  - Minutes, 1962-1981; Series 1 Subseries 1; 1 Cubic Feet
    Scope and Contents
    Contains the minutes of the meetings of the Women's Committee.
  - Annual Reports, 1968-1980; Series 1 Subseries 2; 0.25 Cubic Feet
    Contains the annual reports of the Women's Committee activities on behalf of the Gallery. These reports are general in nature and cover all aspects of the Women's Committee activities.
  - By-Laws, 1968-1984; Series 1 Subseries 3; 0.25 Cubic Feet
    Contains the by-laws of the Women's Committee and chronicles the changes and addenda to those by-laws over the years.
- Activities, 1956-1984; Series 2; 1.75 Cubic Feet
  Organized into three subseries: Balls, Art tours, and Lecture series.
  - Balls, 1956-1983; Series 2 Subseries 1; 1 Cubic Feet
    Contains correspondence, guest lists, sample tickets, planning notes, Programs, post-event reports, decoration schemes and themes for the annual benefit ball put on by the Women's Committee.
  - Art tour, 1962-1970; Series 2 Subseries 2; 0.5 Cubic Feet
    Contains correspondence, guest lists, subscription lists, lecture, programs, post tour reports, and itinerary for tour of art in private homes.
  - Lecture series, 1956-1970; Series 2 Subseries 3; 0.25 Cubic Feet
    Contains lecture possibilities, correspondence, subscription, sample tickets, programs and refreshment lists/plans.
- Treasurer's records, 1959; Series 3; 1 Cubic Feet
  Contains ledgers of income, expenses, and fundraising profits. Also shows record of gifts to Gallery through efforts of the women's committee.
- Ephemera, undated; Series 4; 0.25 Cubic Feet
  Contains scrapbooks of clippings that document the Women's Committee activities and the public reaction to those activities. Also contains photograph albums showing a pictorial history of the Women's Committee and those who supported it.
- Women's Committee files, 1954-1993; Series 5
  Arranged in original order.
  - Meeting of Women's Committee 1954-1959, Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Meeting of Women's Committee 1960-1965, Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting of Women's Committee 1966-1969, Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting of Women's Committee 1970-1975, Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Meeting of Women's Committee 1976-1979, Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Donantion's by Women's Committee, 1972-1973; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gallery #30 1963-1964, Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Misc Materials 1968-1969, Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meeting of Women's Committee 1980-1985, Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Meeting of Women's Committee 1973-1978, Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Meeting of Women's Committee 1980-1988, Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Loose Papers / Invitation, 1977-1987; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Special Committee Confidential, 1989 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fables, Folktales, Myths, 1988; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CGA Mrs. Wynant Vanderpool Jr. 1968 News Articles, Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bank Deposits 1960s, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Paid Bills and Ticket Sales, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Publicity, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Women's Committee Vouchers, 1959-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Deposits from Accoridan Folder, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Deposit Slips, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Deposit Slips, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Ledger and Check Stubs 1960s, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ledger, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Riggs National Bank x2, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ledger x2, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Women's Committee - Records, Letters etc Financial, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Women's Committee Special, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Women's Committee Reg Bank Vouchers, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Women's Committee Special, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Women's Committee Corcoran Vouchers, 1959; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Women's Committee Corcoran Financial, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Printmaking Proposal, Undated; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Women's Committee Reports, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Loose Documents, 1960-1969; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Libations Beverages, 1984-1988; Series 5 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Women's Committee Reference File, 1958-1989; Series 5 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Loose Documents, Undated; Series 5 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Women's Committee Meeting Minutes, 1958-1982; Series 5 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Loose Documents, Undated; Series 5 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The 33rd Corcoran Ball [1 of 3], 1988; Series 5 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The 33rd Corcoran Ball [2 of 3], 1988; Series 5 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The 33rd Corcoran Ball [3 of 3], 1988; Series 5 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Music Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1969 Corcoran Ball Report, Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Invitations Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dinners Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Arrangements Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Lists Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Spring Dance, 1966; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chairman Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Secretary Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Seating See Reservations Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Corcoran Dance Reports, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Minutes Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Corcoran Dance Miscellaneous, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Letters written Ball Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Treasures Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Publicity Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Misc. Ball, 1964; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Mr. WIlliams Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Buffet Liquors Corcoran Dance, 1965; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Publicity Ball, 1964; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Arrangements Ball, 1964; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Reservations Ball, 1964; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Buffet Ball, 1964; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Music Ball, 1964; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Decorations Ball, 1964; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - "Regrets" Ball, 1964; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Printing Ball, 1964; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Invitations Ball, 1964; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Treasurer Ball, 1964; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Ball Tickets, 1963; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Ball Table Decorations, 1963; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Ball Invitations, 1963; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Ball Decorations, 1963; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Ball Supper, 1963; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Ball Publicity, 1963; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Ball Music, 1963; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Ball Misc., 1963; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Spring Dance, Circa 1955-1969; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Ball: 1962 Reports, Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Invitations - Samples (Thouse Sent in Previous Years), 1959; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Spring Dance General Financial, 1961; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Spring Dance General Correspondence + Memos, 1961; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1966; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Spring Dance Press Releases, Clippings, 1961; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1955-1969; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Supper Dance 1962 Corcoran Ball 1968, 1962-1968; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Ticket Info Ball, 1959; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Centennial Ball - Press Releasae, 1959; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1970; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1958; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - [Loose Documents], 1957; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Night of Stars Ball, 1957; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Dali Preview, Circa 1955-1969; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Corcoran Ball Report, 1972; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - General Corresondenc Ball, 1959; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Grand Ball, Decor, 1959; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Decor for Annual Ball, 1958 April; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Ball Correspondence, 1959; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1967; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - 1957 Publicity, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1973 Publicity, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1974 Finances/Contrabutions, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1974 Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1974 Chairman's Report, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1974 Galelry Correspondence, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1974 Publicity, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1974 Program/Invitation, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1974 Committees/Minutes, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1974 Complimentary Tickets, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 1974 Music, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1974 Decorations, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 1974 Luncheon, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 1975 Finances/Contributions, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 1975 Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 1975 Chairman's Report, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 1975 Gallery Correspondence, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 1975 Publicity, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 1975 Program/Invitation, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 1975 Committee, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 1975 Complimentary Tickets, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 1975 Seating/Door List, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 1976 Contrabutions/Finance, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - 1976 Gallery Correspondence, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 1976 Publicity, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - 1976 Program/Invitation, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - 1976 Committee/Minutes, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - 1976 Door List, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - 1976 Music, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - 1976 Complementary Tickets/Staff Discount, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - 1976 Decorations, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - 1976 Reservations, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - 1976 Time Table, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - 1977 Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - 1977 Committees/Minutes, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - 1977 Complementary TIckets, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - 1977 Decoration, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - 1977 Dinner, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - 1977 Door List/Reserevations, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - 1977 Finances/Contrabutions, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - 1977 Finances (bills), Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - 1977 Gallery Correspondence, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - 1977 Invitation, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - 1977 Publicity/Decoration Photos, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - 1977 Program/Invitation, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - 1978 Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - 1978 Complementary Tickets/Staff Discount, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - 1978 Correspondence, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - 1978 Committees, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - 1978 Decorations, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - 1978 Dinner, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - 1978 Finances (Bills), Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - 1978 Finances (contrubutions), Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - 1978 Music, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - 1978 Program/Invitations, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - 1978 Publicity, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - 1978 Seats/Door List, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - 1979 Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - 1979 Correspondence, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - 1979 Dinner, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - 1979 Finances (Contribution), Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - 1979 Program/Invitation, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - 1979 Finances (bills), Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - 1979 Committee/Minutes, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - 1979 Decorations, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - 1979 Music, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - 1979 Publicity, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - 1979 Tea, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - 1979 Seat/Door List, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - 1980 Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - 1980 Committee/Minutes, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - 1980 Complementary Tickets, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - 1980 Decorations, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - 1980 Door List/VIP Invite List, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - 1980 Finances (contributions), Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - 1980 Finances (bills), Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - 1980 Gallery Correspondence, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - 1980 Menu, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - 1980 Music, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - 1980 Program Invitation, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - 1980 Publicity, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - 1981 Seating Door List, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - 1981 Music, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - 1981 Invitations/Programs, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - 1981 Menu, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - 1981 Complimentary Tickets, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - 1981 Arrangements, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - 1981 Correspondence, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - 1981 Finances (bills), Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - 1981 Committee/Minuntes, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - 1981 Finances (contrabuutions), Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - 1981 Correspondence, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - 1981 Complementary Tickets, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - 1981 Chairman's Report, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - 1981 Decorations, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - 1981 Publicity, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - 1982 Seating/Door List, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - 1982 Finances (contrabution), Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - 1982 Invitation/Program, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - 1982 Decoration, Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - 1982 Finances (bills), Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - 1982 - Arrangement, Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 1)